sign-in with Apple was a feature announced by Apple and 2019 and it
使用 Apple 登录是Apple 和 2019 年宣布的一项功能，它
allows users to authenticate into a web or mobile application using their Apple
允许用户使用他们的 Apple ID 对 Web 或移动应用程序进行身份验证，
ID it works just like other one-click social sign-in methods like Google
它的工作原理与其他一键式社交登录方法（如 Google
Facebook Twitter etc to implement this method in your firebase app you'll first
Facebook Twitter 等）一样来实现这一点在您的 Firebase 应用程序中使用方法，您首先
need to have an Apple Developer account which will run you about $99 per year
需要拥有一个 Apple Developer 帐户，该帐户每年将运行您大约 99 美元
now head over to your Apple developer portal create a new app ID or update an
现在前往您的 Apple 开发人员门户创建一个新的应用程序 ID 或更新现有的应用程序 ID
existing one to use the sign-in with Apple capability from there you'll
以使用Apple 登录 从那里您将
create a new service ID and configure it to work with your domain enter the
创建一个新的服务 ID 并将其配置为与您的域一起使用
hosting URLs from your firebase project then register the service ID now we need
从您的 firebase 项目中输入托管 URL然后注册服务 ID 现在我们需要
to verify ownership of this domain with Apple go back to the configuration for
向 Apple 验证该域的所有权返回到
the service ID you'll see the option to download a file save that file under the
配置 服务 ID，您将看到下载文件的选项，将该文件保存
well-known directory in your public hosting folder then upload this file to
在公共托管文件夹中的知名目录下，然后
firebase hosting by running firebase deploy from the command line click
通过从 命令行单击
verify and you should get a green check mark now the last thing we need is a
验证，您现在应该得到一个绿色复选标记我们需要的最后一件事是
private key click on keys and then generate a new one for Apple sign-in go
私钥单击密钥然后为Apple登录生成一个新的
ahead and download this file somewhere securely on your system then open it in
继续并将此文件安全地下载到系统上的某个位置然后打开它 此时在
your editor at this point we can go to the authentication tab on the firebase
您的编辑器中，我们可以转到Firebase 控制台上的身份验证选项卡
console and click enable for Apple sign-in enter your team ID as well as
，然后单击启用 Apple登录输入您的团队 ID 以及
the information from the private key and now we just need to add a little bit of
来自私钥的信息，现在我们只需要添加一点
JavaScript to our front-end app with firebase initialized we'll make a
JavaScript 到我们的前端应用程序初始化了firebase，我们将
reference to auth then we'll define an async function called sign in with Apple
引用auth，然后我们将定义一个名为sign in with Apple的异步函数
it instantiates an auth provider for apple calm then awaits the auth sign in
它实例化一个auth provider forapple静然后等待auth
with pop-up method this prompts the user to login with their Apple ID and when
使用弹出方法登录 提示用户使用他们的 Apple ID 登录，
they're done they'll be logged into the firebase app and will have access to
完成后他们将登录到firebase 应用程序，并可以访问
their user data on the result this has been Apple sign-in with firebase in 100
他们的用户数据，结果是 Apple 在 100 秒内使用 firebase 登录
seconds and I realize that was super fast so head over to fire ship IO to get
，我意识到 那是 超级快，所以前往发射船 IO 以获取
a full step-by-step breakdown of the process thanks for watching make sure to
该过程的完整分步细分感谢您的观看，请务必
LIKE and subscribe and I will see you in the next one
喜欢并订阅，我会在下一个看到你